<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arthur&#39;s Ridiculous Text Expression Machine</title>
    <link>http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Arthur&#39;s Ridiculous Text Expression Machine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 22:35:32 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Everlasting by ddrkirby</title>
      <link>http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/performance/music/love-everlasting-by-ddrkirby/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 22:35:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/performance/music/love-everlasting-by-ddrkirby/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;when-the-outro-came-in:f452199f65a771ade9252ead898f6acb&#34;&gt;When the Outro came in&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was listening to this &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dHMNeNapL1E&#34;&gt;Extra Credits&lt;/a&gt; episode when I heard this outro at the end of the video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&#34;420&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/EnbhV3zuTj8&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The title is &lt;strong&gt;Love Everlasting&lt;/strong&gt; by &lt;em&gt;ddrkirby&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;em&gt;ddrkirby&lt;/em&gt; is an indie composer who happens to produce some awesome 8-bit styled music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The song captivated me because of its strong nostalgia factor, reminiscent of the old 8-bit video game era days. It is an era where video game landscape is almost all 2D. Most of the games then have simple but catchy soundtracks that made their impression on children.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It reminds me of the original Sonic the Hedgehog(1991) soundtrack, with tunes like &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rNxcJDfkrE8&#34;&gt;Marble Zone&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3fzHm23srkI&#34;&gt;Star Light Zone&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are one of those players who grew up in the 90&amp;rsquo;s, then give this a listen. It might lead you to pleasant stroll throught the memory lane of your childhood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;more-on-ddrkirby:f452199f65a771ade9252ead898f6acb&#34;&gt;More on &lt;em&gt;ddrkirby&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Checkout out the rest of the album tracks in this &lt;a href=&#34;http://ddrkirbyisq.bandcamp.com/album/love-everlasting&#34;&gt;site&lt;/a&gt;. If you want to know more about &lt;em&gt;ddrkirby&lt;/em&gt;, you might want to checkout her &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/user/DDRKirbyISQ/featured&#34;&gt;youtube channel&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://sites.google.com/site/ddrkirby/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Vector Art</title>
      <link>http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/visual/drawing/starting-vector-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2015 15:44:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/visual/drawing/starting-vector-art/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-other-side-of-the-fence:29de3aa4c61cac74984fb82cb265c6f3&#34;&gt;The other side of the fence&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have always been fascinated with the Internet. The process of creating a website has always involved both disciplines. A beautiful website needs to exercise both the creative and logical.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am only familiar with the coding side of the equation as a web developer. I haven&amp;rsquo;t explored the visual aspects of creating a website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I decided that learning the process of asset creation would benefit me. Even surface knowledge would be enough. Knowing myself, I would be happy creating things considered mundane by professional designer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;choosing-the-method:29de3aa4c61cac74984fb82cb265c6f3&#34;&gt;Choosing the method&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;digital-painting:29de3aa4c61cac74984fb82cb265c6f3&#34;&gt;Digital Painting&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the obvious which is &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Digital_painting&#34;&gt;digital painting&lt;/a&gt;. It is the most common and most versatile method of creating digital art. Why not go with this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, I would have to abstain from it right off the bat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Financial reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe that to create digital paintings, you need a drawing tablet. Unfortunately, I am too poor to afford one right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, I will pass on this one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/Z8xkYpC.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Examples&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;pixel-art:29de3aa4c61cac74984fb82cb265c6f3&#34;&gt;Pixel Art&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I grew up with 8-bit and 16-bit video games. Most of those games at that time use &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pixel_art&#34;&gt;pixelized art&lt;/a&gt; rather than the smooth and clean methods that we have today. This method holds some nostalgic value for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But creating it takes a lot of hard work and dedication. Resizing it to fit many resolutions is also going to be a nightmare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I always smile when I see pixel art. But I will just enjoy looking at rather than creating it when it comes to the web.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/eKkBRUb.png&#34; alt=&#34;Examples&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;vector-art:29de3aa4c61cac74984fb82cb265c6f3&#34;&gt;Vector Art&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vector_graphics&#34;&gt;Vector Art&lt;/a&gt; consists of lines and gradients that are created via mathematical models rather than painting them as pixels. In the end, this is the one that I chose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t need to have a tablet&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People can create amazing vector with just a mouse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Assets created in vector art can be resized to fit any resolution&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will be designing sites with an eye on mobile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Vector art lends itself well to flat design&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/Jtwcp1g.png&#34; alt=&#34;Examples&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;choosing-what-software-to-use:29de3aa4c61cac74984fb82cb265c6f3&#34;&gt;Choosing what software to use&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on my research, there are only really 2 contenders for this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.adobe.com/products/illustrator.html&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adobe Illustrator&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pro

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Industry Standard&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Con

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very Expensive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://inkscape.org/en/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inkscape&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pro

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Con

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not a good choice if you are going for a professional career in Vector art&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since I am just getting my feet wet with vector graphics, it is better to start with the free option.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inkscape it is!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;first-vector-art:29de3aa4c61cac74984fb82cb265c6f3&#34;&gt;First Vector Art&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I decided to just spice up the background of my &lt;a href=&#34;http://arvinsim.github.io&#34;&gt;github organization page&lt;/a&gt; with a throwaway vector art made up of simple geometric shapes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used triangles and squares to create a simple mosaic background.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/ln01b2N.png&#34; alt=&#34;Vector Art 1&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Mirror Season 1 Episode 2</title>
      <link>http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/performance/tv/black-mirror-season-1-episode-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 15:00:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/performance/tv/black-mirror-season-1-episode-2/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;details:f809e3f55e3fcaeb9cf53f6bad8ec67c&#34;&gt;Details&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Title: &lt;strong&gt;Five Million Credits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Episode: 2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Season: 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;description:f809e3f55e3fcaeb9cf53f6bad8ec67c&#34;&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The protagonist is woken up by a virtual rooster in walled room composed of screens. We are then introduced to his daily routine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brushing off his teeth. Cycling on a stationary bike to earn &amp;ldquo;credits&amp;rdquo;, which is the currency of this world. Daily bombardment of commercial advertisement and porn that cannot be looked away unless you incur a penalty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then a day came when he hears a beautiful song from a woman. It awakens him from his apathy and he got into a conversation with her. He convinces her that her voice is good enough for a reality TV show. The woman just brushes it off as flattery at first. Further interactions with lessened her hesitation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, their interactions culminated in his offer of giving her a very expensive gold ticket to a &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_X_Factor&#34;&gt;X-Factor&lt;/a&gt; like reality TV show, &lt;em&gt;Hot Shot&lt;/em&gt;. The woman initially hesitates but finally relents. They are now on the road of possible greatness. Or perhaps something different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;review:f809e3f55e3fcaeb9cf53f6bad8ec67c&#34;&gt;Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world here is a dystopia that reminds me of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fahrenheit_451&#34;&gt;Fahrenheit 451&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Running_Man_(1987_film)&#34;&gt;The Running Man&lt;/a&gt;. It also reminds me of contemporary shows like American Idol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems that the world became fully integrated with technology. No clues were given on the state of the world outside the microcosm that the shows provide unlike films like &lt;em&gt;The Matrix&lt;/em&gt;. We learn later that the stationary bikes power the electricity of the &lt;em&gt;Hot Shot&lt;/em&gt; show. I assume that it probably powers all electricity in the state though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People are bombarded daily with advertisements via the screens in their room. You can&amp;rsquo;t look away because the advertisement pause until it can track your eyeballs looking at the screen. The show makes it clear that pornography has became legalized, accepted and ubiquitous. You can&amp;rsquo;t also escape the reality TV show &lt;em&gt;Hot shots&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world primary means of communication and entertainment is thru apps. Lots and lots of apps. Apps as mundane as a virtual chicken alarm clock to First Person Shooters without direction to virtual Gurus and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The show seem to be railing against consumerism, obsession with technology, mindless entertainment, forced advertising and superficiality.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The War of Art</title>
      <link>http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/literary/the-war-of-art-book-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 22:42:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/literary/the-war-of-art-book-review/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;details:f8cd6a78e60b83800c58e39b789b8533&#34;&gt;Details&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Title: The War of Art&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Author: Steven Pressfield&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publication Date: 2002&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publisher: Black Irish Books&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ISBN: 978-1-936891-02-3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-did-you-read-the-book-what-made-you-interested-in-it:f8cd6a78e60b83800c58e39b789b8533&#34;&gt;Why did you read the book? What made you interested in it?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I discovered the book while I was reading a Reddit post about Enterprenuerial books. It was recommending good books to read for the budding entrepreneur. While I was browsing the list, this book caught my eye. I surmised that it is because of the title. It is remniscent of Sun Tzu&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Art_of_War&#34;&gt;The Art of War&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After doing some research, I gave it a try since it is a short book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-did-you-read-it:f8cd6a78e60b83800c58e39b789b8533&#34;&gt;How did you read it?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I read this book in short bursts. I don&amp;rsquo;t have much reading time as I used to since I now have lots of hobbies and side projects to attend to. I choose my morning ride from home to the office as my reading time for this book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The book consists of small sections with each section expounding on a one line idea. My morning ride consists of going to a street where a particular jeep is passing. I get off and then transfer to the jeep which takes me to my office location.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As it turns out, the book divisions and my transportation routine lend themselves to each other very well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;can-you-give-a-brief-summary-of-the-book:f8cd6a78e60b83800c58e39b789b8533&#34;&gt;Can you give a brief summary of the book?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first part of the book introduces us to the concept of &lt;em&gt;Resistance&lt;/em&gt;. The author gives a definition, explains it&amp;rsquo;s many forms and symptoms, and gives some examples of situations where &lt;em&gt;Resistance&lt;/em&gt; is holding us back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second part of the book gives advice on how to deal with &lt;em&gt;Resistance&lt;/em&gt;. He starts with some tips but switches his strategy by using the contrast between a &lt;em&gt;Professional&lt;/em&gt; and a &lt;em&gt;Amateur&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last part of the book deals more with the metaphysical. He uses colorful terminology in his explanations for this part. For example, he uses the terms &lt;em&gt;muses&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;angels&lt;/em&gt; as a designation to these mysterious forces. The rest of the book deals with how to invoke these forces, the dichotomy of the &lt;em&gt;ego&lt;/em&gt; and the &lt;em&gt;self&lt;/em&gt;, as well as the &lt;em&gt;territorial&lt;/em&gt; and the &lt;em&gt;hierarchial&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-insights-did-you-get-from-the-book:f8cd6a78e60b83800c58e39b789b8533&#34;&gt;What insights did you get from the book?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the parts where I can relates is where he says that those close to you will act strangely if you try to change your life. It can be changing careers, lifestyle, diet, etc. Some will conciously or unconciously try to sabotage you. When I tried to change my dietary methods, suffice not everyone was estatic with it. Some expressed doubts, some tried to tempt me to break my diet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also like the implication that the worst enemy of our success is ourselves. It might be depressing to think that we were holding ourselves back all long. But think of it this way, you have the power to improve yourself if you just choose to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, I find the idea of the &lt;em&gt;Professional&lt;/em&gt; reassuring. I am the type of person who tries to be good at whatever he is doing. Lots of advice in the &lt;em&gt;Professional&lt;/em&gt; section resonate with me. I have no problem agreeing with the author in that section.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-your-recommendation:f8cd6a78e60b83800c58e39b789b8533&#34;&gt;What is your recommendation?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first two parts of the book has some interesting ideas and information that you can use to apply to your life. They are useful when trying to get out of a rut or mental/creative block.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is the third part where I think it gets less interesting. By trying to use some concepts such as &lt;em&gt;muses&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;angels&lt;/em&gt;, it gives off a &amp;ldquo;new age&amp;rdquo; feel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not to say that it is bad. But I went to read this book for some pragmatic concepts that can be applied directly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether you like it or not, this book is short so it is worth a try.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Words from the Three Tools of Death</title>
      <link>http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/literary/logophilia-january-31-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 23:01:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/literary/logophilia-january-31-2015/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;After being busy for about a year, I finally decided to return reading on one of my favorite British author/philosopher, &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/G._K._Chesterton&#34;&gt;G.K. Chesterton&lt;/a&gt;. His writings are dense and take time to digest. I decided to start with his most accessible writings, his &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Father_Brown&#34;&gt;Father Brown&lt;/a&gt; Mysteries. I just randomly opened a page and I happened on the &amp;ldquo;The Three Tools of Death&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;cataract:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Cataract&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a descent of water over a steep surface; a waterfall, especially one of considerable size.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;gaeity:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Gaeity&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a happy and lively quality&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;puritanical:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Puritanical&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;very strict in moral or religious matters, often excessively so; rigidly austere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;dram:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Dram&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a small drink of liquor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;prosaic:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Prosaic&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;commonplace or dull; matter-of-fact or unimaginative:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;impinge:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Impinge&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;to strike; dash; collide (usually followed by on, upon, or against):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;sable:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Sable&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the color black, often being one of the heraldic colors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;baronet:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Baronet&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a member of a British hereditary order of honor, ranking below the barons and made up of commoners, designated by Sir before the name and Baronet&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;hedge:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Hedge&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a row of bushes or small trees planted close together, especially when forming a fence or boundary&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;totter:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Totter&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;to walk or go with faltering steps, as if from extreme weakness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;chap:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Chap&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a fellow; man or boy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;enliven:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Enliven&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;to make sprightly or cheerful; brighten:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;stolid:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Stolid&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;not easily stirred or moved mentally; unemotional; impassive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;provincial-furniture:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Provincial - furniture&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;having or showing the manners, viewpoints, etc., considered characteristic of unsophisticated inhabitants of a province; rustic; narrow or illiberal; parochial&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;draught:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Draught&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a current of air, esp one intruding into an enclosed space&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;exuberance:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Exuberance&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the state of being exuberant; effusively and almost uninhibitedly enthusiastic; lavishly abundant:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;tweed:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Tweed&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a coarse wool cloth in a variety of weaves and colors, either hand-spun and handwoven in Scotland or reproduced, often by machine, elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;aspen:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Aspen&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;any of various poplars, as Populus tremula, of Europe, and P. tremuloides (quaking aspen) or P. alba (white aspen) of America, having soft wood and alternate ovate leaves that tremble in the slightest breeze.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;grizzled:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Grizzled&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;having gray or partly gray hair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;bristle:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Bristle&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;one of the short, stiff, coarse hairs of certain animals, especially hogs, used extensively in making brushes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;incongruity:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Incongruity&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the quality of being incongruous; out of keeping or place; inappropriate; unbecoming:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;read-from:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Read from&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Book: &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.gutenberg.org/ebooks/204&#34;&gt;The Innocence of Father Brown&lt;/a&gt;, part of the &lt;em&gt;Father Brown Mysteries&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chapter: &amp;ldquo;The Three Tools of Death&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Author: G.K. Chesteron&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;definition-reference:0a0b28d65bd7a713eaa5008bf99a894c&#34;&gt;Definition Reference&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dictionary.com/&#34;&gt;dictionary.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Mirror Season 1 Episode 1</title>
      <link>http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/performance/tv/black-mirror-season-1-episode-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 15:00:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/performance/tv/black-mirror-season-1-episode-1/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;details:dd909382ff31b3d167bc91250317a093&#34;&gt;Details&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Title: &lt;strong&gt;The National Anthem&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Episode: 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Season: 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;description:dd909382ff31b3d167bc91250317a093&#34;&gt;Description&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The British Prime Minister wakes up with a call from one of his aides. He is shown a video feed informing him that the Princess was abducted by some unknown person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They then get to the end of the video where the Princess was forced to recite the demand of the kidnapper. In a bizarre twist, the simple demand turned out to be utterly morbid. Worse, the word has gotten out about the whole incident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With no clues as to the whereabouts of the kidnapper, will they be able to rescue the Princess before the Prime Minister gives in to the demand?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;review:dd909382ff31b3d167bc91250317a093&#34;&gt;Review&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where do I start?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just watched the first episode and it completely blew me away! I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen any TV series this decade which deals with issues raised by the digital age in a serious manner. The first episode forces you to think about social media, journalism, the public&amp;rsquo;s fickleness and fascination with the morbid and even the nature of art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No wonder some people are already dubbing it as &amp;ldquo;The Twilight Zone for the digital age&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a great start to a series. I&amp;rsquo;m sure I will be watching the next episodes.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>