<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Keto on Arthur&#39;s Ridiculous Text Expression Machine</title>
    <link>http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/tags/keto/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Keto on Arthur&#39;s Ridiculous Text Expression Machine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 22:27:11 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/tags/keto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini Western Omelette</title>
      <link>http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/culinary/mini-western-omelette/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 22:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/culinary/mini-western-omelette/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;For this week, I choose to cook a variation of an omelette that has a distinctive western taste.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week, I made Quiche using spinach and broccoli. The meal tasted great and satiated my hunger easily when I ate it for lunch and dinner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Valentines Day is upcoming and there are many other things that I need to attend to this week. Because of that, I want to cook a meal that is easy to prepare and has less green vegetables as ingredients. I was able to get a recipe from &lt;a href=&#34;http://cavemanketo.com/mini-western-omelettes/&#34;&gt;Caveman Keto&lt;/a&gt; that seems fit the bill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;differences:fb513274b0fcb8302e3b4b73088399e9&#34;&gt;Differences&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ham steak is expensive and hard to find in our area. Cooked or spiced ham on the other hand is plentiful and cheap. Since this is not the main ingredient, I choose to buy the less expensive option.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheddar cheese is no longer a rare sight in supermarkets anymore. But they cost twice as much as the ordinary ones. I figure out that I can live with the latter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The placement of sliced cheese in the recipe just doesn&amp;rsquo;t sit well with me. I prefer the cheese grated or sliced into cubes to be mixed into the egg batter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;lessons:fb513274b0fcb8302e3b4b73088399e9&#34;&gt;Lessons&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I should have put baking cups in the muffin pan. The omelettes cooked fine without them. But it was a pain when I tried to clean them after cooking. I submerged the muffin pan in water to soften the sticky leftovers. Even so, it was hard to scrape them off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I tried putting grated cheese on some omelettes while I put small cheese cubes for the others. After trying both, the omelettes with the cubes retained its taste better. The grated cheese melded with the egg batter and it did not taste as good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;screenshots:fb513274b0fcb8302e3b4b73088399e9&#34;&gt;Screenshots&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/GsN2d3Dh.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/GsN2d3Dm.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mini western omelettes in a container&#34;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/OqzAkkih.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/OqzAkkim.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Another picture of mini western omelettes&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/fgMj1xuh.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/fgMj1xum.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;A single mini western omelette&#34;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>