<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on Arthur&#39;s Ridiculous Text Expression Machine</title>
    <link>http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/tags/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on Arthur&#39;s Ridiculous Text Expression Machine</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 22:47:15 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/tags/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Booksale: In Defense of Food</title>
      <link>http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/literary/booksale-in-defense-of-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 22:47:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://arvinsim.github.io/artem/literary/booksale-in-defense-of-food/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was browsing the book selection of Booksale&amp;rsquo;s branch in Gaisano last week. I was looking for a certain &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Founders_at_Work&#34;&gt;book&lt;/a&gt; that I am sure I saw before. I examined as many books that I could-going as far as inspecting the books in the lower shelves. Unfortunately, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to find it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, I was supposed to buy some groceries for my weekly meals after work. But it bugged me that I was only able to partially examine the book selection the last time I visited. So I decided to pay Booksale another visit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were 2 books that interested me. One was a book on &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Compilers:_Principles,_Techniques,_and_Tools&#34;&gt;compilers&lt;/a&gt; that is affectionaly called the &amp;ldquo;Red Dragon Book&amp;rdquo;. This book is worth 175Php. The other one was a &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/In_Defense_of_Food&#34;&gt;book&lt;/a&gt; about food nutrition and diet. It piqued my interest since it was the 102th recommended book in Reddit&amp;rsquo;s top favorite book list. This book is worth 60php.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was hard choosing which one to buy. But I decided to buy the book on food for many reasons. It was cheap. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t get as outdated as fast as technology books. I am also confident that there are free resources in the internet that is as comprehensive as the &amp;ldquo;Red Dragon&amp;rdquo; book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/oxa6dUo.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/oxa6dUom.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;In Defense of Food - An Eater&#39;s Manifesto&#34;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>